towerpopup.com 2011-06-13

# Privacy Policy | real estate news and housing | TowerPopUp.com

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Google Adsense and DoubleClick DART cookie   
Google, as a provider of advertising of others, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of cookies by DART enables them to serve Google ads to visitors who are depending on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. 

DART to remove cookies, you can view listings from Google and privacy policy of the content network at the following address http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html track users through the mechanisms are under DART cookie its own privacy policies of Google. 

Other third-party servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track user activities on this site to measure advertising effectiveness and other reasons which will be provided in their own privacy policies, news of the Real Estate and Housing | TowerPopUp.com has no access or control over these cookies that can be used by third party advertisers. 

Collection of Personal Information   
When visiting new real estate and housing | TowerPopUp.com, the IP address used to access the site will be connected with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements and gather broad demographic information for internal use. More importantly, all registered IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Links to Other Sites   
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on those sites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of those sites may differ from ours. 

Changes to this privacy statement   
The content of this statement may be amended at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have questions regarding the privacy policy of new real estate and housing | TowerPopUp.com then you can contact us at advertisin6@yahoo.com 

This policy was generated by Easy Privacy Policy Plugin churchill car insurance for WordPress. Last updated Sat, December 18, 2010 4:22
